压制:随Feng
Set The Fire To Rain
歌手：Adele 阿黛尔
我把心 抛下
I let it fall, my heart
坠落之际 你挺身认领
And as it fell, you rose to claim it
漆黑一片 我命休矣
It was dark and I was over
这时你吻我唇 救我一命
Until you kissed my lips and you saved me
我这双手 苍劲有力 可双膝却弱不禁风
My hands, they were strong, but my knees were far too weak
站在你怀里 才不会瘫倒于地
To stand in your arms without falling to your feet
可你藏有一面 不曾为我知 为我知
But there's a side to you that I never knew, never knew
你所有的言语 不曾发于心 发于心
All the things you'd say, they were never true, never true
你所有的游戏 赢家总是你 总是你
And the games you'd play, you would always win, always win
而我烧起了一场雨
But I set fire to the rain
轻抚你脸庞 细看雨滂沱
Watched it pour as I touched your face
雨在烧 我落泪
Well, it burned while I cried
因为我听到它在拼命喊着你 喊着你
'Cause I heard it screaming out your name, your name
与你共枕 我方可暂留那儿
When laying with you I could stay ther
合上双眼 感受你永留这儿
Close my eyes, feel you here forever
你与我手相携 胜过世间一切
You and me together, nothing is better
可你藏有一面 不曾为我知 为我知
'Cause there's a side to you that I never knew, never knew
你所有的言语 不曾发于心 发于心
All the things you'd say, they were never true, never true
你所有的游戏 赢家总是你 总是你
And the games you'd play, you would always win, always win
而我烧起了一场雨
But I set fire to the rain
轻抚你脸庞 细看雨滂沱
Watched it pour as I touched your face
雨在烧 我落泪
Well, it burned while I cried
因为我听到它在拼命喊着你 喊着你
'Cause I heard it screaming out your name, your name
我烧起了一场雨
I set fire to the rain
再把你我丢进火海
And I threw us into the flames
雨正酣 了一念
While it fell, something died
因为我知道了却的是前缘 是前缘
'Cause I knew that that was the last time, the last time
有时我于门口醒来
Sometimes I wake up by the door
你曾捕获的心定是在等你
That heart you caught must be waiting for you
尽管如今 你我再无瓜葛
Even now when we're already over
我仍禁不住要把你找寻
I can't help myself from looking for you
我烧起了一场雨
I set fire to the rain
轻抚你脸庞 细看雨滂沱
Watched it pour as I touched your face
雨在烧 我落泪
Well, it burned while I cried
因为我听到它在拼命喊着你 喊着你
'Cause I heard it screaming out your name, your name
我放火烧了雨
I set fire to the rain
再把你我丢进火海
And I threw us into the flames
雨正酣 了一念
While it fell, something died
因为我知道了却的是前缘 是前缘 噢
'Cause I knew that that was the last time, the last time, oh
噢 不
Oh, no
让雨烧 噢
Let it burn, oh
让雨烧
Let it burn
我烧起了一场雨
I set fire to the rain
再把你我丢进火海
And I threw us into the flames
我感觉到什么东西死亡了
While it fell, something died
因为我知道 那是最后一次 最后一次 哦
'Cause I knew that that was the last time, the last time, oh
压制:随Feng
噢 不
Oh, no